'use client'
const data = [
    {
        'question': 'Ms. Ortega’s development team contributed ——– to the successful launch of the newest mobile application.',
        'choices': ['automatically', 'substantially', 'sharply', 'accordingly'],
        'answer': 'substantially',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'In order to meet production targets, inspection equipment that breaks down easily should be checked on a ——– basis.',
        'choices': ['regular', 'regularly', 'regularize', 'regularity'],
        'answer': 'regularly',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': '——– you experience any problems with the building’s equipment, you should contact the property manager.',
        'choices': ['Becauseof', 'Incaseof', 'Immediately', 'If'],
        'answer': 'If',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Employees must park in the ——- parking lot until the renovation of the company building is completed.',
        'choices': ['frequent', 'generous', 'complicated', 'temporary'],
        'answer': 'temporary',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Although the assembly machine has been used for more than 20 years, it is still ——–.',
        'choices': ['annual', 'experienced', 'operational', 'previous'],
        'answer': 'operational',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Medical ——– are supposed to investigate the characteristics and effects of newly developed materials.',
        'choices': ['expert', 'expertise', 'experts', 'expertly'],
        'answer': 'experts',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Darwin Construction, renowned for its ——– designs, has won the bid for the Dalton City Library.',
        'choices': ['innovation', 'innovate', 'innovatively', 'innovative'],
        'answer': 'innovative',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Please make sure that ——– address is correct in the designated section of the order form.',
        'choices': ['yours', 'yourself', 'your', 'you'],
        'answer': 'your',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'Mr. Thompson was ——– as the marketing director after a successful market development in Asia.',
        'choices': ['appointing', 'appointed', 'appoint', 'appoints'],
        'answer': 'appointed',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },
    {
        'question': 'The Irwin City Tourist Information Office is ——– located in the center of the city.',
        'choices': ['particularly', 'unfortunately', 'absolutely', 'conveniently'],
        'answer': 'conveniently',
        'initialValue': 'Not answered'
    },

];

export default data;